[
    {
        "question": "Rubaiya said, \"I had never been there before.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "Rubaiya",
          "1": "she",
          "3": "before",
          "2": "never",
          "5": "that",
          "6": "was",
          "7": "been",
          "8": "I",
          "9": "there",
          "10": "said",
          "11": "had"
        },
        "answers":[[4,10,5,1,11,2,7,9,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aditi told Rakesh, \"He is a nice man now.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "Rakesh",
          "1": "Aditi",
          "3": "he",
          "2": "man",
          "5": "is",
          "6": "nice",
          "7": "now",
          "8": "was",
          "9": "told",
          "10": "that",
          "11": "then",
          "12": "a"
        },
        "answers":[[1,9,4,10,3,8,12,6,2,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jewel said to Chandrani, \"I can help you tomorrow.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "Chandrani",
          "1": "day",
          "3": "he",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "Jewel",
          "6": "help",
          "7": "can",
          "8": "Chandrani",
          "9": "said",
          "10": "tomorrow",
          "11": "that",
          "12": "next",
          "13": "could",
          "14": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,14,8,11,3,13,6,4,2,12,1],[5,9,14,4,11,3,13,6,8,2,12,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Asha said, \"If I lose my job now, I shall die.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "she",
          "1": "die",
          "3": "her",
          "2": "Asha",
          "5": "job",
          "6": "if",
          "7": "then",
          "8": "said",
          "9": "would",
          "10": "lost",
          "11": "that",
          "12": "she",
          "13": "had"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,11,6,12,10,3,5,7,4,9,1],[2,8,11,6,4,10,3,5,7,12,9,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Asha said, \"If I lost my job then, I would die.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "she",
          "1": "die",
          "3": "have",
          "2": "Asha",
          "5": "job",
          "6": "if",
          "7": "then",
          "8": "said",
          "9": "would",
          "10": "lost",
          "11": "that",
          "12": "she",
          "13": "had",
          "14": "died",
          "15": "her"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,11,6,12,13,10,15,5,7,4,9,3,14],[2,8,11,6,4,13,10,15,5,7,12,9,3,14]]
    },
    {
        "question": "\"I know that God is great\", cried Bibhas.",
        "words": {
          "4": "God",
          "1": "saying",
          "3": "knows",
          "2": "he",
          "5": "Bibhas",
          "6": "that",
          "7": "was",
          "8": "knew",
          "9": "is",
          "10": "cried",
          "11": "great",
          "12": "that"
        },
        "answers":[[5,10,1,6,2,8,12,4,9,11],[5,10,1,12,2,8,6,4,9,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bibhas said, \"I know that a great thing happened in my life then.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "great",
          "1": "said",
          "3": "knew",
          "2": "happened",
          "5": "a",
          "6": "his",
          "7": "Bibhas",
          "8": "he",
          "9": "then",
          "10": "in",
          "11": "that",
          "12": "had",
          "13": "life",
          "14": "thing",
          "15": "known",
          "16": "that"
        },
        "answers":[[7,1,16,8,3,11,5,4,14,12,2,10,6,13,9],[7,1,11,8,3,16,5,4,14,12,2,10,6,13,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bibhas said, \"I knew that a great thing happened in my life then.\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "great",
          "1": "said",
          "3": "knew",
          "2": "had happened",
          "5": "a",
          "6": "his",
          "7": "Bibhas",
          "8": "he",
          "9": "then",
          "10": "in",
          "11": "that",
          "12": "was",
          "13": "life",
          "14": "thing",
          "15": "had known",
          "16": "that",
          "17": "happened"
        },
        "answers":[[7,1,16,8,15,11,5,4,14,2,10,6,13,9],[7,1,11,8,15,16,5,4,14,2,10,6,13,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She said that she didnâ€™t want to come with me.",
        "words": {
          "4": "to",
          "1": "with",
          "3": "I",
          "2": "she",
          "5": "want",
          "6": "said",
          "7": "you",
          "8": "come",
          "9": "go",
          "10": "don't"
        },
        "answers":[[2,6,3,10,5,4,9,1,7]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Deb said to Shubhashree that he was thinking of her.",
        "words": {
          "4": "Shubhashree",
          "1": "had",
          "3": "Deb",
          "2": "I",
          "5": "of",
          "6": "have",
          "7": "said",
          "8": "you",
          "9": "thinking",
          "10": "to",
          "11": "thought",
          "12": "been",
          "13": "am"
        },
        "answers":[[3,7,10,4,2,13,9,5,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She cried to say that I had not visited her for many years.",
        "words": {
          "4": "me",
          "1": "not",
          "3": "for",
          "2": "years",
          "5": "she",
          "6": "did",
          "7": "you",
          "8": "visit",
          "9": "cried",
          "10": "many",
          "11": "had",
          "12": "visited"
        },
        "answers":[[5,9,7,6,1,8,4,3,10,2]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sabita said that I had been playing cricket when she had seen me.",
        "words": {
          "4": "you",
          "1": "cricket",
          "3": "had",
          "2": "Sabita",
          "5": "you",
          "6": "I",
          "7": "were",
          "8": "when",
          "9": "playing",
          "10": "said",
          "11": "seen",
          "12": "saw"
        },
        "answers":[[2,10,5,7,9,1,8,6,12,4],[2,10,4,7,9,1,8,6,12,5]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dilip said to his mother that he would be late that night.",
        "words": {
          "4": "mother",
          "1": "I",
          "3": "Dilip",
          "2": "shall",
          "5": "his",
          "6": "late",
          "7": "to",
          "8": "be",
          "9": "said",
          "10": "tonight",
          "11": "should",
          "12": "that night"
        },
        "answers":[[3,9,7,5,4,1,2,8,6,10]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I said that I knew that if I had said something wrong there, the teacher would have punished me.",
        "words": {
          "4": "punished",
          "1": "had",
          "3": "something",
          "2": "teacher",
          "5": "have",
          "6": "that",
          "7": "the",
          "8": "I said",
          "9": "there",
          "10": "I",
          "11": "I knew",
          "12": "wrong",
          "13": "me",
          "14": "would",
          "15": "if",
          "16": "said",
          "17": "that"
        },
        "answers":[[8,17,11,6,15,10,1,16,3,12,9,7,2,14,5,4,13],[8,6,11,17,15,10,1,16,3,12,9,7,2,14,5,4,13]]
    }
]